MkvDrama.me
MkvDrama.me
This series is a work of fiction. It is not related to any real persons, places, organizations, or events.
هذه السلسلة عمل خيالي، لا علاقة لها بأي أشخاص أو أماكن أو منظمات أو أحداث حقيقية.
Shall we take them now, boss?
هل نأخذهم الآن يا رئيس؟
You're Sia Tep?
أنت سيا تيب؟
Why’d you kill my dad?!
لماذا قتلت والدي؟!
Hey! Keen!
مهلا! كين!
You killed my dad.
لقد قتلت والدي.
Why’d you kill my dad?!
لماذا قتلت والدي؟!
Your dad, Kanchit, stole my money!
والدك كانشيت سرق أموالي!
Pakorn and I have prepared everything.
لقد قمت أنا وباكورن بتحضير كل شيء.
So for today’s first match, I’m putting Thun in the ring.
لذا في أول مباراة اليوم، سأضع ثون في الحلبة.
Are you sure everything will be okay?
هل أنت متأكد أن كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام؟
Hey, Yut’s using a weapon!
مهلا، يوت يستخدم سلاحا!
Thun!
ممتاز!
Thun! You asshole!
ثون! أيها الأحمق!
Safe House
بيت آمن
(Ten minutes earlier)
(قبل عشر دقائق)
Alright, everyone, listen to me carefully.
حسنًا، أيها الجميع، استمعوا إليّ بعناية.
Pakorn and I have prepared everything.
لقد قمت أنا وباكورن بتحضير كل شيء.
You don’t need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
First, we need to make this place as chaotic as possible
أولاً، علينا أن نجعل هذا المكان فوضويًا قدر الإمكان
to create a distraction.
لخلق تشتيت.
Everyone, run! Quickly!
الجميع، اركضوا! بسرعة!
Run, everyone! Run! Hurry!
اركضوا جميعًا! اركضوا! أسرعوا!
Then I’ll be the one to hit the switch to help Thun and Keen escape.
ثم سأكون الشخص الذي يضغط على المفتاح لمساعدة ثون وكين على الهروب.
As for you two..
أما بالنسبة لكما..
Hey!
يا!
Our plan is to draw their attention away.
خطتنا هي أن نلفت انتباههم بعيدًا.
We’ve got intruders inside! Get in here and help!
لدينا متسللون بالداخل! ادخلوا وساعدونا!
Go, hurry!
اذهب، اسرع!
This way!
من هنا!
Damn, the door’s locked!
لعنة، الباب مغلق!
Dad, Let me try.
أبي، دعني أحاول.
You check the back door.
تحقق من الباب الخلفي.
You two come with me to the front, quick!
تعالوا معي إلى الأمام بسرعة!
Hey, guard this door.
مهلا، احرس هذا الباب.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Hurry up!
اسرع!
Hey!
يا!
I told you, didn’t I?
لقد قلت لك، أليس كذلك؟
You’ll never escape me.
لن تهرب مني أبدًا.
Is this all you’ve got?
هل هذا كل ما لديك؟
Pathetic.
مثير للشفقة.
You love him that much, huh?
أنت تحبه كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
Huh?!
هاه؟!
You really love him?
هل تحبينه حقا؟
Good!
جيد!
Then I’ll take everything that’s yours and make it mine.
ثم سأأخذ كل ما هو لك وأجعله ملكي.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
ما الذي حدث لك بحق الجحيم؟
What’s wrong with me?
ماذا بي؟
You want to know what the fuck is wrong with me?
هل تريد أن تعرف ما هو الخطأ معي؟
It’s because of you!
إنه بفضلك!
I have to be like this.
يجب أن أكون هكذا.
Pakorn loves you.
باكورن يحبك.
Pakorn helps you.
باكورن يساعدك.
And the one who had to suffer for it was me!
والذي كان عليه أن يعاني من ذلك هو أنا!
And now you still have the nerve to ask me that?
والآن هل مازلت تملك الجرأة لتسألني ذلك؟
Are you ready to play with me, darling?
هل أنت مستعد للعب معي يا عزيزتي؟
I won’t let you lay a finger on Keen.
لن أسمح لك بوضع إصبعك على كين.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Hey, how are you guys?
مرحبا، كيف حالكم يا رفاق؟
Barely made it. What about the others?
بالكاد وصلت. ماذا عن الآخرين؟
Right?
يمين؟
Yeah, what about Typhoon?
نعم، ماذا عن تايفون؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
What about Thun and Keen?
ماذا عن ثون وكين؟
I haven’t seen them.
لم ارىهم
What do we do now?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
Shit.
اللعنة.
They’re here! Hey, they’re here!
إنهم هنا! هم هنا!
Thun! Keen!
ثون! كين!
How are you guys?
كيف حالكم يا شباب؟
We’re okay.
نحن بخير.
But the door’s locked, what now?
ولكن الباب مغلق، ماذا الآن؟
What do we do?
ماذا نفعل؟
Bung!
يا صديقي!
What are you doing, Mai?
ماذا تفعلين يا ماي؟
What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟!
Got it!
فهمتها!
Hey, how’d you do that?
مهلا، كيف فعلت ذلك؟
I saw it online, bro.
لقد رأيته على الإنترنت يا أخي.
Here’s the key!
وهنا المفتاح!
Go! Get out, quick!
إذهب! إخرج بسرعة!
Hey! Get out!
مهلا! اخرج!
Hurry!
عجل!
Move!
يتحرك!
Hey!
يا!
Coach! Dad!
مدرب! أبي!
Hey, Dad!
مرحبا يا أبي!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
You need to run.
يجب عليك الركض.
Take care of yourself, okay?
اعتني بنفسك، حسنًا؟
Go.
يذهب.
Dad, open the door! Hey!
أبي، افتح الباب! هي!
Don’t you dare hurt my dad!
لا تجرؤ على إيذاء والدي!
Hey, bro!
مرحباً يا أخي!
Bro!
أخ!
Pakorn and Typhoon are still inside!
باكورن وتايفون لا زالوا بالداخل!
Stop.
قف.
Dad!
أب!
Get out of the way
ابتعد عن الطريق
Let's go. Just go!
هيا بنا. فقط اذهب!
Go now!
اذهب الآن!
Think you’re so tough, huh?
هل تعتقد أنك قوي جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Calm down first.
اهدأ أولاً.
Die!
ال!
Hey!
يا!
I'll take care of it.
سأعتني بالأمر.
Are you sure you want to go in there?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد الدخول هناك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You’re all look like a mess.
أنتم جميعا تبدو وكأنكم في حالة من الفوضى.
Hey, who’s that lady over there?
مهلا، من تلك السيدة هناك؟
Shhh, quiet.
ششش، هدوء.
Go clean yourself first, then we’ll talk.
اذهب ونظف نفسك أولاً، وبعد ذلك سنتحدث.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Whoa, how’d you do that?
واو، كيف فعلت ذلك؟
I'll try too.
سأحاول أيضا.
I can’t do it.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
You have to blow gently.
يجب عليك النفخ بلطف.
I did it!
أنا فعلت هذا!
Ow!
أوه!
Sorry.
آسف.
It's the internal wound from a blow.
إنه الجرح الداخلي الناتج عن ضربة.
At least you're still alive.
على الأقل أنت لا تزال على قيد الحياة.
Ait…
الانتماء…
Do you know that Dad always does everything for me?
هل تعلم أن أبي يفعل كل شيء من أجلي دائمًا؟
I want to do something for him too.
أريد أن أفعل شيئاً له أيضاً.
I want to make him proud for once.
أريد أن أجعله فخوراً مرة واحدة.
Hey..
يا..
Please stay calm, okay?
من فضلك ابقى هادئا، حسنا؟
Like Keen said, Pakorn and Typhoon are still inside.
كما قال كين، باكورن وتايفون لا زالا بالداخل.
At least we should trust them, right?
على الأقل يجب علينا أن نثق بهم، أليس كذلك؟
Stay calm.
ابقى هادئا.
We’ll get through this together.
سوف نتجاوز هذا معًا.
So you've been like this since you were a kid?
هل كنت هكذا منذ أن كنت طفلاً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Why?
لماذا؟
No reason, I won’t judge.
لا يوجد سبب، لن أحكم.
Hey!
يا!
What is it? Let me see.
ما هو؟ دعني أرى.
No.
لا.
Come on, let me see!
تعال، دعني أرى!
Why are you getting shy?
لماذا أنت خجول؟
Let me see, come on.
دعني أرى، هيا.
Nope.
لا.
I wasn’t handsome back then.
لم أكن وسيمًا في ذلك الوقت.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Just don’t make fun of me.
فقط لا تسخر مني.
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
It’s kinda cute.
إنه لطيف نوعا ما.
You were a crybaby too, weren’t you?
لقد كنت تبكي أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Well, boxing hurts, okay?
حسنًا، الملاكمة تؤلم، أليس كذلك؟
But you’ve come this far, well, what a good boy.
لكنك وصلت إلى هذا الحد، حسنًا، يا له من فتى جيد.
Oh, so now you're messing with my head, huh?
أوه، إذن أنت الآن تتلاعب برأسي، أليس كذلك؟
Hey!
يا!
Now you're messing with my head? Stop!
الآن أنت تعبث بعقلي؟ توقف!
Let go.
اتركه.
No!
لا!
Ow!
أوه!
Ait, I have a surprise for you.
أيت، لدي مفاجأة لك.
What?
ماذا؟
Kaew!
يا!
Kaew, are you safe?
كايو هل أنت آمن؟
I’m fine. What about you?
انا بخير. ماذا عنك؟
Yeah, I’m fine.
نعم، أنا بخير.
Look at me, I’m strong as ever.
انظر إليّ، أنا قوي كما كنت دائمًا.
Let go!
اتركه!
Ow!
أوه!
Hey, Kaew.
مهلا، كايو.
Don’t forget to take your meds, water and eat well, okay?
لا تنسى أن تأخذ أدويتك والماء وتأكل جيدًا، حسنًا؟
So we can meet again soon.
حتى نتمكن من الالتقاء مرة أخرى قريبا.
Okay.
تمام.
Ait, are you crying?
أيت، هل تبكي؟
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
I’m not crying!
انا لا ابكي!
Mawin, please take care of my brother, okay?
ماوين، من فضلك اعتني بأخي، حسنًا؟
Of course, Kaew. I’ll take great care of him.
بالطبع، كايو. سأعتني به جيدًا.
Don’t you say.
لا تقولي ذلك.
I’m the one who should be taking care of you.
أنا من يجب أن يعتني بك.
But how did you end up there, Kaew?
ولكن كيف انتهى بك الأمر هناك، كايو؟
P’Klao came to pick me up.
لقد جاء P'Klao ليأخذني.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hi.
أهلاً.
Say thanks to Pakorn and Thun, not me.
قل شكرًا لباكورن وثون، وليس لي.
I’m really grateful to you.
انا شاكر لك جدا.
Go thank Pakorn and Thun!
اذهب وشكر باكورن وثون!
(Klao, right? I've beem waiting.)
(كلاو، صحيح؟ لقد كنت أنتظر.)
Hey, you again…
مرحبا بك مرة أخرى...
We meet again, Klao.
لقد التقينا مرة أخرى، كلاو.
What’s going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I’ve got something I’d like your help with.
لقد حصلت على شيء أريد مساعدتك فيه.
Let me hang up first.
دعني أعلق أولاً.
I've got to get Kaew’s meds ready.
يجب أن أحصل على أدوية كاو جاهزة.
Okay.
تمام.
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
Bye, Ait. Bye, Mawin.
وداعا أيت. وداعا ماوين.
Bye, Kaew.
وداعا، كايو.
Bye-bye!
وداعا وداعا!
Get plenty of rest.
احصل على قسط كبير من الراحة.
Wait, P’Klao!
انتظر، بكلاو!
You hung up?
هل أغلقت الهاتف؟
If I’d known, I wouldn’t have let you talk to her.
لو كنت أعلم، لم أكن لأسمح لك بالتحدث معها.
I didn’t even get to talk to Klao.
ولم أتمكن حتى من التحدث مع كلاو.
You guys, seriously…
يا رفاق، بجدية...
If it weren’t for your dad, who knows what could’ve happened to Klao and Kaew.
إذا لم يكن والدك، فمن يدري ماذا كان يمكن أن يحدث لكلاو وكايو.
So what do we do next?
إذن ماذا نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Honestly, I'm still not sure.
بصراحة، أنا لست متأكدًا بعد.
All we know is that we have to help Uncle Petch.
كل ما نعرفه هو أن علينا مساعدة العم بيتش.
If I’d just listened to Mom from the beginning,
لو كنت استمعت إلى أمي منذ البداية،
none of this would’ve happened.
لا شيء من هذا كان ليحدث.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
She told me to quit boxing.
لقد طلبت مني أن أتوقف عن الملاكمة.
If I hadn’t been a boxer, none of this might’ve happened.
لو لم أكن ملاكمًا، لم يكن من الممكن أن يحدث أي شيء من هذا.
It’s not because you were a boxer.
ليس لأنك كنت ملاكمًا.
Don’t blame boxing.
لا تلوم الملاكمة.
Of course it was.
بالطبع كان كذلك.
You probably think I'm old-fashioned
ربما تعتقد أنني من الطراز القديم
always trying to hold you back.
يحاول دائما أن يمنعك.
But think about it,
ولكن فكر في الأمر،
what kind of mother wants to see her child getting hurt?
أي نوع من الأمهات تريد أن ترى طفلها يتأذى؟
I could give you everything,
أستطيع أن أعطيك كل شيء،
and yet, you still insisted on boxing.
ومع ذلك، كنت لا تزال تصر على الملاكمة.
But…
لكن…
If you hated boxing so much,
إذا كنت تكره الملاكمة كثيرًا،
why did you marry Dad?
لماذا تزوجت من أبي؟
You and Dad were different.
لقد كنتما مختلفين.
He had no other choice.
ولم يكن لديه خيار آخر.
I loved him because he fought for everything.
لقد أحببته لأنه حارب من أجل كل شيء.
He did everything for the people he loved.
لقد فعل كل شيء من أجل الأشخاص الذين أحبهم.
We struggled together until your grandparents finally agreed to let us marry.
لقد ناضلنا معًا حتى وافق أجدادك أخيرًا على السماح لنا بالزواج.
And he promised me he’d quit boxing.
ووعدني بأنه سيتوقف عن الملاكمة.
But one day, he left me and you to go work with those people.
ولكن في يوم من الأيام، تركني وتركك ليذهب للعمل مع هؤلاء الأشخاص.
I always thought something was off.
اعتقدت دائمًا أن هناك شيئًا خاطئًا.
Turns out, I was right.
اتضح أنني كنت على حق.
Just look at the two of you now.
فقط أنظر إلىكما الآن.
Let’s not dwell on the pain of the past.
دعونا لا نركز على آلام الماضي.
What matters most now is your happiness.
ما يهم الآن هو سعادتك.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
You’re just like your father,
أنت مثل والدك تماما
get scolded a little and you act all mopey.
تتعرض للتوبيخ قليلاً وتتصرف وكأنك حزين.
Thun, go help Mom in the kitchen.
ثون، اذهب لمساعدة أمي في المطبخ.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Smells amazing, Bung.
رائحته مذهلة، بونج.
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
We haven’t eaten anything since this morning.
لم نأكل أي شيء منذ هذا الصباح.
Thank you, Mom.
شكرا لك أمي.
Thanks!
شكرًا!
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Mai,
يمكن،
I’m not eating this. You want it?
أنا لا آكل هذا. هل تريده؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Extra.
إضافي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thanks.
شكرا. شكرا لك.
Eat up. You need strength.
كُل، أنت بحاجة إلى القوة.
Yeah.
نعم.
So, how long have you two been together?
إذن، منذ متى وأنتما معًا؟
For a little while now, Mom.
منذ فترة قصيرة يا أمي.
You guys are official?
هل أنتم رسميون؟
What, you didn’t know?
ماذا، لم تعرف؟
You knew too?
هل عرفت أيضا؟
Everyone at the gym knows.
الجميع في صالة الألعاب الرياضية يعرفون ذلك.
Just eat already.
فقط تناول الطعام بالفعل.
And no need to do the dishes after,
ولا داعي لغسل الأطباق بعد ذلك،
I’ll have the maid take care of it.
سأطلب من الخادمة أن تعتني بالأمر.
No, it’s okay. I feel bad, I’ll help clean up.
لا، لا بأس. أشعر بالسوء، سأساعد في التنظيف.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I’m just worried you’ll break something
أنا قلق فقط من أنك سوف تكسر شيئًا ما
these dishes are expensive.
هذه الأطباق غالية الثمن.
So when did you guys start dating?
إذن متى بدأتم المواعدة؟
Why didn’t I know anything about this?
لماذا لم أعرف شيئا عن هذا؟
Jeez, Mai, why are you so curious?
يا إلهي، ماي، لماذا أنت فضولية جدًا؟
What? It’s just about being a couple.
ماذا؟ الأمر يتعلق فقط بكوننا زوجين.
Why all the secrecy?
لماذا كل هذا السرية؟
Actually, Mai’s got a point.
في الواقع، ماي لديها نقطة.
You and Ait are flirty and never had to hide.
أنت وأيت مغازلان ولم تضطرا أبدًا إلى الاختباء.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
Eat a lot, I don’t want you to be hungry.
تناول الكثير من الطعام، لا أريدك أن تشعر بالجوع.
Aw, how thoughtful. Thanks.
أوه، كم هو مُفكّر. شكرًا.
I just don’t want you to be hungry.
أنا فقط لا أريدك أن تكون جائعًا.
I’ll stop talking now.
سأتوقف عن الحديث الآن.
Wow, we’re about to have some real drama.
واو، نحن على وشك أن نشهد بعض الدراما الحقيقية.
Wanna try me?
هل تريد أن تجربني؟
No, it’s okay. The porridge is already great.
لا، لا بأس. العصيدة لذيذة بالفعل.
Everyone..
الجميع..
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Pick it up, Keen.
إلتقطها، كين.
(MP Phuwit)
(النائب فويت)
Keen.
حريص.
Gotta hand it to you.
يجب أن أسلمك إياه.
You did great leading everyone to escape.
لقد قمت بعمل رائع في مساعدة الجميع على الهروب.
I really underestimated you.
لقد قللت من شأنك حقا.
But unlucky for you, your Coach Petch didn’t get away.
ولكن لسوء حظك، مدربك بيتش لم يتمكن من الهرب.
What did you do to Uncle Petch?
ماذا فعلت لعم بيتش؟
Don’t you dare hurt him!
لا تجرؤ على إيذائه!
What do you want from us?
ماذا تريد منا؟
Relax, your Coach Petch is safe.
استرخي، مدربك بيتش في أمان.
But you already know what I want.
لكنك تعرف بالفعل ما أريد.
Give me the code.
أعطني الكود.
Otherwise, he’ll end up just like your father, Kanchit.
وإلا فإنه سينتهي تمامًا مثل والدك، كانشيت.
Die the same way.
مت بنفس الطريقة.
Keen, don’t believe him!
كين، لا تصدقه!
He’s going to kill Uncle Petch anyway.
إنه سيقتل العم بيتش على أية حال.
Dad…
أب…
Don’t you dare hurt my dad!
لا تجرؤ على إيذاء والدي!
Calm down. Don’t touch my dad!
اهدأ. لا تلمس أبي!
You.
أنت.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
This won’t help anything.
هذا لن يساعد في أي شيء.
Don’t you dare touch Uncle Petch.
لا تجرؤ على لمس العم بيتش.
If you lay a finger on him, don’t expect me to give you that code.
إذا وضعت إصبعك عليه، فلا تتوقع مني أن أعطيك هذا الرمز.
If anything happens to him.. even a scratch..
إذا حدث له أي شيء.. حتى لو كان خدشًا..
I’ll destroy the code.
سأدمر الكود.
You know what kind of person I am.
أنت تعرف أي نوع من الشخص أنا.
Ha!
ها!
Nice try, Keen. You think you can fool me?
محاولة جيدة يا كين. هل تظن أنك تستطيع خداعي؟
If you had the code from the start, none of this would’ve…
لو كان لديك الكود منذ البداية، فلن يحدث أي شيء من هذا...
Twenty-four words.
أربع وعشرون كلمة.
The code is a 24 English words, right?
الكود عبارة عن 24 كلمة انجليزية، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
Yeah.. back then, I didn’t have it.
نعم.. في ذلك الوقت، لم يكن لدي ذلك.
But now I do.
ولكن الآن أفعل ذلك.
Jonathan
جوناثان
Give Uncle Petch back,
أعيدوا العم بيتش،
and I’ll give you the code.
وسأعطيك الكود.
Where?
أين؟
Somewhere crowded.
مكان مزدحم.
Then let’s do it at my Heaven’s Arena match this Friday.
إذن فلنفعل ذلك في مباراتي في Heaven's Arena يوم الجمعة القادم.
Come quickly, and be on time.
تعال بسرعة، وكن في الوقت المحدد.
My Jonathan is very hungry.
جوناثان جائع جدًا.
You’re lucky, Coach Petch.
أنت محظوظ، يا مدرب بيتش.
Keen, you have the code?
كين، هل لديك الرمز؟
Nope.
لا.
Then why the hell did you agree to give it to him?
إذن لماذا وافقت على إعطائه له؟
What if we can’t find it in time?
ماذا لو لم نتمكن من العثور عليه في الوقت المناسب؟
Or do you want to see your dad get hurt?
أم تريد أن ترى والدك يتأذى؟
Bro…
أخ…
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Maybe Keen already has a plan.
ربما يكون لدى كين خطة بالفعل.
Right now, this really is our best shot.
في الوقت الحالي، هذه هي أفضل فرصة لدينا حقًا.
Keen, what exactly is the code?
كين، ما هو الكود بالضبط؟
It’s a wallet.
إنها محفظة.
The code is supposed to be 24 random words.
من المفترض أن يتكون الكود من 24 كلمة عشوائية.
But why does that bastard want the code so bad?
ولكن لماذا يريد هذا الوغد الكود بشدة؟
Because…
لأن…
The money in the wallet…
المال في المحفظة…
It’s the money my dad stole from him.
إنها الأموال التي سرقها والدي منه.
I’m sorry.
أنا آسف.
I only just found out myself.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك بنفسي للتو.
So all of this is because of you?
فكل هذا بفضلك؟
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
Hey.
يا.
But everyone here’s a victim of that bastard too.
لكن الجميع هنا هم ضحايا لهذا الوغد أيضًا.
Mawin
ماوين
It’s okay, I’ll check on him.
لا بأس، سأتحقق منه.
Keen,
حريص،
where did your dad hide the code?
أين أخفى والدك الرمز؟
We’ll help look for it together.
سنساعدك في البحث عنه معًا.
Uh…
أوه…
I still have no idea.
لا زلت ليس لدي أي فكرة.
Then why did you promise him?
إذن لماذا وعدته؟
What if you can’t find it?
ماذا لو لم تتمكن من العثور عليه؟
Keen…
حريص…
Thun, just go back.
ثون، فقط ارجع.
You can leave me here.
يمكنك تركي هنا.
Where’d you get this?
من أين حصلت على هذا؟
When I was little and throwing tantrums,
عندما كنت صغيرًا وأثير نوبات الغضب،
Mom used to bring out these sparkler sticks to calm me down.
كانت أمي تحضر لي هذه العصي المشتعلة لتهدئتي.
It’d ease my mind for a moment.
سوف يريح ذهني للحظة.
So whenever I feel bad,
لذلك كلما شعرت بالسوء،
I light a sparkler.
أشعلت شرارة.
I think it might help you too.
أعتقد أنه قد يساعدك أيضًا.
That’s very sweet. Thanks.
هذا لطيف جدًا. شكرًا.
I know how you feel.
أنا أعرف كيف تشعر.
In the past,
في الماضي،
I didn’t want anyone to see me
لم أكن أريد أن يراني أحد
during the weakest time.
خلال الأوقات الأضعف.
I just didn’t want you to see me like this.
لم أرد أن تراني بهذه الطريقة.
I’m afraid you’d feel bad too.
أخشى أنك ستشعر بالسوء أيضًا.
But now we have each other, Keen.
لكن الآن لدينا بعضنا البعض، كين.
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
I’ll always be by your side.
سوف أكون بجانبك دائمًا.
Looks like it’s going to rain.
يبدو أن المطر سوف يهطل.
Come on, I want to take you somewhere.
تعال، أريد أن آخذك إلى مكان ما.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Where are you taking me, Thun?
إلى أين تأخذني يا ثون؟
Come on.
تعال.
It’s dark.
إنه الظلام.
Wait a sec…
انتظر ثانية…
Hey, this is the same place from the photo in your room!
مهلا، هذا هو نفس المكان من الصورة في غرفتك!
Yeah.
نعم.
Watch this.
شاهد هذا.
Whoa, how’d you do that?
واو، كيف فعلت ذلك؟
Here, try it.
هنا، جربه.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Yum.
يم.
It’s raining, let’s head back.
إنها تمطر، دعنا نعود.
You’ve been practicing this since you were a kid?
هل كنت تمارس هذا منذ أن كنت طفلاً؟
Yeah. Took years to get it right.
نعم، استغرق الأمر سنوات حتى أصبح الأمر صحيحًا.
Why is there a mattress here?
لماذا يوجد مرتبة هنا؟
Back then, when Mom and Dad had a fight,
في ذلك الوقت، عندما تشاجر أمي وأبي،
I’d sneak out and sleep here.
سأتسلل وأنام هنا.
Ah… like your safe zone?
أه... مثل منطقتك الآمنة؟
It’s sweet. Wanna try?
إنه حلو. هل تريد تجربته؟
Mmm… it is very sweet.
ممم... إنه لطيف جدًا.
At least something good happened today.
على الأقل حدث شيء جيد اليوم.
Who knows what tomorrow holds.
من يعلم ماذا سيحدث غدا.
Let it be tomorrow’s problem.
لتكن مشكلة الغد.
Keen.
حريص.
Thun.
ثون.
That wasn’t so hard.
لم يكن ذلك صعبا للغاية.
There’s no puzzle we can’t solve.
لا يوجد لغز لا يمكننا حله.
Sometimes the answer we’re looking for is easier than we think.
في بعض الأحيان تكون الإجابة التي نبحث عنها أسهل مما نعتقد.
If we just open our hearts.
إذا فتحنا قلوبنا فقط.
Thun…
ثون…
Wake up.
استيقظ.
What is it, Keen?
ما الأمر يا كين؟
I know where we need to go.
أنا أعلم إلى أين نحتاج أن نذهب.
Then I’ll give you a chance to prove yourself.
ثم سأعطيك فرصة لإثبات نفسك.
Bring Thun, Keen, and the code.
أحضر ثون وكين والرمز.
Are you sure about going there?
هل أنت متأكد من الذهاب إلى هناك؟
If it were Dad, he’d definitely hide the code there.
لو كان أبي، فإنه بالتأكيد سيخفي الرمز هناك.
There’s no puzzle we can’t solve.
لا يوجد لغز لا يمكننا حله.
Sometimes the answer is simpler than we think.
في بعض الأحيان تكون الإجابة أبسط مما نعتقد.
Everyone around me has a reason to betray me.
كل من حولي لديه سبب لخيانتي.
No matter where we go, we go together.
أينما ذهبنا، فنحن نذهب معًا.
Keen, watch out.
كن حذرا، كن حذرا.
You're the only person I have left.
أنت الشخص الوحيد الذي بقي لي.